(大蛇丸)サスケ！
Sasuke!
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
Eye of
the Hawk
(大蛇丸)何だろう？ これ。
(三代目)おお！ よく見つけたな。
What is this?
Ah! How lucky of you to find this.
これは 白蛇の脱皮した皮だ。
It's the skin of a white snake.
初めて見た こんなの。
I've never... seen anything
like it before.
ハハッ 実はワシもだよ。
Actually, neither have I.
それは滅多に見ることのできない
珍しいものだぞ。
It's a rare item that
you almost never see.
どうして 白いの？
さあな よくはわかっておらん。
Why is it white?
Well, I don't really know.
そんなこと誰も気にとめんしな。
No one really cares about
such things.
ただ 昔から白蛇は 幸運と
再生の象徴とされとるんだ。
But from times past,
the white snake has been
a symbol of good luck and renewal.
幸運と再生…。
Good luck and renewal...
ここで見つけたのも何かの因縁。
It must be some sort of karma
for you to find it here.
お前の両親も どこかで生まれ
変わっているかもしれんのお。
Perhaps your parents are
now reborn somewhere.
いつかまた
大きくなったお前と会うために。
Maybe someday...
you'll meet them when you're grown up.
それって いつだろう？
さてなあ。
When would that be...?
Who knows? I couldn't say.
それはわからんが。
《縄樹 気負ってるわね》
Nawaki... sure is eager.
≪戦争だからね 今は≫
We're at war... after all.
綱手の小隊が？
Tsunade's team has been...?
(綱手)止まれ！ 止まれ！
止まれ！ 止まれってんだ！
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I said, stop!
もうよせ 死んでる。
あ～っ！
That's enough! He's dead!
《人は何て壊れやすいものなの》
Humans... are such fragile beings.
《人体には 一生のうちに➡
Power that was not used in a lifetime
rests inside the human body.
使われることのない力が
眠っている。
その力を解放できれば…！》
If we could release that power...
(アンコ)大蛇丸先生！
これ何です？
Orochimaru-sensei!
What is this?
お守りよ。
お守り？ これが!?
An amulet.
An amulet...? This...?
フフッ それはね
とっても珍しい➡
It's a very rare amulet for
good luck and renewal.
再生と幸運のお守りなのよ。
再生？ これで？
Renewal? With this...?
でも いくら大蛇丸先生が
研究熱心だとしても➡
But... Orochimaru-sensei,
no matter how earnest you are
about your research,
死んじゃった人は
生き返らないですよね？
you can't bring back the dead,
can you?
そうね。
死者の復活は難しいわね。
Yes... Bringing the dead
back to life is difficult.
でもね 再生のヒントなら
掴んでるの！
But, I've grasped a clue
about regeneration.
肉体を活性化させることで
人は格段に強くなり➡
By activating their bodies,
humans can become immensely
more powerful
それと同時に
再生力も高まるのよ。
and heighten their regenerative powers too.
あなたにもいずれ
その力を分けてあげるわね。
I will share that power
with you some day, as well.
はい！ ありがとうございます！
大蛇丸先生！
Yes! Thank you very much,
Orochimaru-sensei!
《呪印という名の
肉体活性術をね》
The Body Activating Jutsu
called the Curse Mark...
《大蛇丸 : バカな！
ムチャな修業にもほどがある！》
How foolish!
There's a limit to unreasonable training!
美しい… これが写輪眼の力！
Beautiful...
So this is the power of the Sharingan.
どれほどの忍が この領域に…。
No matter how many Ninja try
to enter this territory...
どれほどの修業をしようと➡
No matter how hard they train,
they could never surpass the Uchiha.
うちはの血を
超えることなんて…。
"ENTRY RESTRICTED"
"TRANSFER"
《わかる…。
I understand...
私には
この術式のすごさがわかる…。
I understand the awesomeness
of this Jutsu...
でも この禁術を会得するのには
最低 １か月…》
But, it would take at least one month
to master this Forbidden Jutsu...
"TRANSFER"
《ここにある術を
すべて会得するのに➡
How many years would it take
to master all the Jutsu that are here...?
いったい何年かかるというの!?
人の持つ
限られた時間のなかでは➡
It's impossible to grasp all the Jutsu
すべての術を
手にすることは不可能。
within the limited time
of a human lifespan...
たとえ 再生忍術で
生き長らえたとしても➡
There would be a limit
even if I could extend my life
via a Reanimation Jutsu...
それは有限。
死ねば すべては失われてしまう》
Once I die, everything would be lost...
《すべてを手に入れるには…》
In order to grasp every Jutsu,
I would have to...
大蛇丸。 やはり キサマか。
Orochimaru! So it was you,
just as I suspected...
言え。 ここで何をやっていた？
Tell me! What were you doing here?
フフフフ… あなたには
理解できないでしょうね。
You probably couldn't understand...
自らの理よりも
里を優先する あなたには。
You who puts the village
before your own reason.
(大蛇丸)私にとって
肉体の寿命は短すぎる。
To me, the lifespan of
the human body is too short.
たとえ 火影と呼ばれようとも➡
Even if I were to be called a Hokage,
死ねば すべては
そこで終わりですから。
once I die,
everything would end there.
まさか… ここで
実験している術は…。
The Jutsu you're experimenting with...
It can't be...?!
その まさか…
不老不死の術ですよ。
That very one...
the Immortality Jutsu!
(自来也)もう考え直しては
くれないのか？ 大蛇丸。
Can't you reconsider Orochimaru?
笑止！
Out of the question!
バカにも程がある。
How stupid can you be?!
《あと一歩…。
I'm so close...
あと一歩のところまで
研究は進んでいる》
So close with my research.
《私は すべてを手に入れる。
I will have everything.
私の器は
この体でも木ノ葉でもない。
My vessel is neither this body,
nor the Leaf!
そのためには 組織だろうと
何だろうと利用するまで！》
To that end, I will use that organization
and anything else!
新しいメンバーの到着だ。
A new member has arrived.
うちはイタチ…。
Uchiha Itachi.
《うちはを滅ぼしたあなたが
暁に来るなんてね…》
You destroyed the Uchiha.
What brings you to the Akatsuki?
貴重な写輪眼を持つ者が
自ら私の前に…。
One who possesses the precious Sharingan
appears before me...
なんてラッキーなのかしら 私は。
How lucky I am...
さあ その体 いただくわよ！
I will have your body!
うっ…。
まさか… この私が
金縛りの幻術に…。
Could it be... that I...
am under a Paralysis Genjutsu...
なんという瞳力… すばらしい!!
What visual prowess...
Marvelous...
うっ…。
(イタチ)大蛇丸
お前のいかなる術も➡
Orochimaru...
Any Jutsu you use will have
no effect before these eyes.
この眼の前では
なんの効力も持たない。
フフフフッ… 来たわね。
You've come.
(さあ 行きましょう))
Now, let's go...
《私の未来は この子の中にある》
My future lies in this child!
(サスケ)終わりか…
あまりにもあっけない。
It's over... That was too quick.
うっ… うぅ…。
フフフフ… そろそろ
効いてきたみたいね。
Looks like it's beginning
to take effect...
この大白蛇の体液は➡
The body fluid of the giant white snake skin
vaporizes upon contact with the air
空気に触れると気化する
痺れ薬なのよ。
and becomes an anesthetic.
私は 不滅。
I am immortal.
あなたごときの術では
まだまだ殺せぬ。
The likes of your Jutsu cannot kill me...!
さあ！ いただくわよ！
Now then...
I shall have you now!
何だ？
(大蛇丸)ここは
私の中にある異空間。
What is this?
This is... a different space inside my body.
ここで転生の儀式を行うのよ。
Here, the Transference Ritual will be held...
始めるわ。
We'll begin now.
《大蛇丸 : なんという瞳力…。
すばらしい。
What visual prowess... Marvelous...
これは まるで あのときの！》
This is almost like... that time...
フフフフフ… ハハハハハ！
その眼… その眼が
ついに私のものに！
Those eyes...
Those eyes will be mine at last...!
《カブト : 薬じゃ もうもたないな…。
He won't last with only the medicine...
早ければ今日にも転生の儀式を
行うしかないか…》
He'll have to do the Transference Ritual
as soon as today...
《しかし あのサスケ君が
素直に うんと言うとは思えない》
But...
It's hard to believe that
Sasuke would consent willingly...
《フン まあ サスケ君といえども
あの儀式には逆らえまいが》
Well, even Sasuke can't resist that ritual...
《どうして サスケ君がここに…。
Why is Sasuke here?!
あれは 巨大ヘビの脱皮。
That is the cast-off skin
of the giant snake...
ということは
すでに 儀式が終わったのか》
Does that mean the ritual
is already done?
《いったい どうなってる？》
What's going on?
カブトか？
Kabuto, is that you?
今のキミは
いったい どっちなんです？
Which one...
are you now?
どっちだと思う？
Which one do you think?
《これは転生の儀式。
転生の儀式の記憶を
見せられているんだ。
This is the Transference Ritual!
He's showing me the memories
of the Transference Ritual!
これから ２人の儀式に
決着がつく》
The ritual between the two
will be settled right now!
((これは…。
What the--?!
(大蛇丸)バカな ここは
私の作り出した異空間よ。
This... can't be...
This is a place I created.
This is impossible...!
ありえない ありえない！
ありえないわ。
Impossible!
ここは私だけの…。
It can't be...
This is my only...!
大蛇丸。
お前のいかなる術も
この眼の前では…。
Orochimaru...
Any Jutsu you use will have
no effect before these eyes.
(もう わかってるはずだろう？))
You... should realize that by now.
《なんて おぞましい。
サスケ君の意思が
空間を侵食していく》
How... hideous...
Sasuke-kun's will is eroding the space!
((大蛇丸 : ああ こんな…
こんなことがあってたまるか！
I'm not... going to let this happen!
私は 不死の大蛇丸だぞ！
I am the immortal Orochimaru!
こんな こんなところで！
Not here!
こんなところで この私が!!
I won't let this happen here!
私は この世を解き明かす者。
I am the one to unravel
the order of this world...!
(すべてを 手にする者なのだ…))
Everything... will be mine!
(ナルト)
なんか イヤな雲行きだってばよ。
The clouds are moving ominously...
まるで…。
(自来也)燃ゆる落日。
Almost like...
A flaming sunset, like blood...
血のようじゃな。
(鬼鮫)どうしました？
いや なんでもない。
What's the matter?
No, it's nothing.
大蛇丸様が 死んだ…。
いや これではまるで…。
Orochimaru-sama is dead.
No... It's almost as if...
オレが ヤツのすべてを
のっとったのさ。
I took over all that he was.
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu wo mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
beyond a great number of promises
ikutsu mono yakusoku no sono ue ni tatte wa
are the words that spilled over from the day as I reflect upon them
kamishimeru ano hi koboreochita kotoba
it's as though I made a vow which expresses these feelings into words
komerareta omoi wa chikai no you de
then it would link the befinning with the present day
kuchi ni sureba ima to hajimari wo tsunagu
it's not in my dreams
yume de wa nakute
that place doesn't exist in a fantasy world either
esoragoto no sekai de mo nai basho de sa
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu no mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukete
embracing the long path ahead
sono zutto saki wo toraeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
Next Episode
Three years have passed since
he broke away all ties,
suppressed his personal feelings
and trained himself,
just so he can achieve his goal...
Now is the time for him to take action
with Orochimaru's power.
(ルーシィ)あぁ 気持いい。
What awaits him, as he pushes his way
through the dark corridor?
やっぱり 自分家は 落ち着くな。
Light or darkness?
(カナ)いいとこね。
でしょ！ ん？
Next time: "Zabuza's Blade"
Zabuza's Blade
私も ここに住もうかな。
ギャ～ッ！